<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>This is a little showcase Fast installation This one-line installation does not support every OS, detail information for different OS can be found in the here
curl -sL &amp;#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pystardust/ytfzf/master/ytfzf&amp;#34; | sudo tee /usr/bin/ytfzf &amp;gt;/dev/null &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo chmod 755 /usr/bin/ytfzf *requires cURL
Features Subscriptions Thumbnails History Download Format selection Queue multiple videos Update-Log We have now added Subscriptions which allows you to search between videos of subscribed channels easily Now ytfzf can queue videos using fzf multiselect option.</description></item><item><title>Usage</title><link>/docs/prologue/examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/docs/prologue/examples/</guid><description>Basic example ytfzf [Options] &amp;lt;search-query&amp;gt; To quit the script you can press ESC or ^C in the video selection prompt.
Configurations You can create a configuration file to manage the different value instead of exporting them.
The configuration file should be:
~/.config/ytfzf/conf.sh If you wish to find inspiration and see an example you can take a look at the sample configuration file
Thumbnails Showing thumbnails requires ueberzug (which works only on X11, not supported on Wayland and MacOS).</description></item><item><title>Config</title><link>/docs/prologue/config/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/prologue/config/</guid><description>~/.config/ytfzf/config.sh #This is the default config file #this file is read when it is placed in ~/.config/ytfzf #keep in mind that this is a .sh file, and can be used as such #this config file can be completely empty and ytfzf will still work (as these are the default settings), #so feel free to get rid of anything you don&amp;#39;t want in here ################### # ENV VARIABLES # ################### #each variable below can be set here, or using export #when setting them through export, use the variable in parentheses instead #variables set through export will override the ones set here #enable/disable history (enabled by default) #history is stored in $history_file ($YTFZF_CACHE/ytfzf_hst by default, change $history_file to change this) #(YTFZF_HIST) enable_hist=1 #enable/disable looping (disabled by default) #when enabled, after a video ends it will bring up the results menu again #(YTFZF_LOOP) enable_loop=0 #the directory to store cache #history, thumbnails, and the currently playing video will be stored here #(YTFZF_CACHE) cache_dir=&amp;#34;$HOME/.</description></item></channel></rss>